<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Unqualified Success</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Unqualified Success</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Captioning Part 4</title>
      <link>/post/ultimate-captioning-disc-detector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ultimate-captioning-disc-detector/</guid>
      <description>Establish a baseline for disc detection.
 Data Calculation of HoGs using varying number of cells and bins Clustering Evaluation Conclusion  Overview Data Source 3471 images, excerpted from 2015bsVriot.mp4, roughly 1 frame per second for about 1 hour.
 Data Preparation Partition the labeled data into two sets: Some portion of the data for training and the rest for testing. For example: 40% training
cd /Users/Karl/Dropbox/Projects/Video-Captioning sh ./partition_data_two_class.sh disc labeled_3471.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Captioning Part 3</title>
      <link>/post/ultimate-captioning-scorecard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ultimate-captioning-scorecard/</guid>
      <description>What tools would make the video captioning task easier? What partial solutions contribute to the whole solution? Since the field, the disc, and the players are the key ingredients for a game, tools focused on detecting these items would be a reasonable place to start.
 Identify images depicting the disc. The disc is particularly hard to find, due to its small size; therefore only detected when white patch exceeds a certain size and white patch is roughly circular (and not a picture of a disk on a sign or banner)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Captioning Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/ultimate-captioning-approaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ultimate-captioning-approaches/</guid>
      <description>How have others approached this problem? What are the key challenges in the field of video captioning? How can we decompose the problem to facilitate solution by parts? How can we leverage the work of others to save time and produce a better solution? What is most interesting, and how do people describe it? How many frames needed to determine action? Using descriptive video services to create a large data source for video annotation research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Captioning Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/ultimate-captioning-problem-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ultimate-captioning-problem-rmd/</guid>
      <description>How can we choose the best 150 two-second plays from 10 or more hours of raw video? Preparing a highlights video from raw footage is an intensely time-consuming endeavor. This post begins with a brief introduction to the sport of Ultimate, followed by an overview of the temporal structure of a game and temporal structure of scoring a single point. The data inventory describes possible sources of information about the game and the post concludes with a glossary and a short list of simplifying assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>